{"test_questions": [[{"question": "A train always has", "opta": "Rails", "optb": "Driver", "optc": "Guard", "optd": "Engine", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which one of the following is always found in 'Bravery'?", "opta": "Experience", "optb": "Power", "optc": "Courage", "optd": "Knowledge", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A song always has", "opta": "Word", "optb": "Chorus", "optc": "Musician", "optd": "Tymbal", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Yesterday I saw an ice cube which had already melted due to heat of a nearby furnace.", "opta": "Always", "optb": "Never", "optc": "Often", "optd": "Sometimes", "ans": "B", "explanation": "Since the ice cube had already melted due to the heat of a nearby furnace so after this ice cannot remain as ice cube."}, {"question": "What is found necessarily in milk?", "opta": "Cream", "optb": "Curd", "optc": "Water", "optd": "Whiteness", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which one of the following is always with 'Bargain'?", "opta": "Exchange", "optb": "Sumptuousness", "optc": "Triviality", "optd": "Eloquence", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which one of the following a 'Drama' must have?", "opta": "Actors", "optb": "Story", "optc": "Sets", "optd": "Director", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A boy is sitting at the back seat of a car. When the driver suddenly starts moving the car (in forward direction), the boy experiences a backward force?", "opta": "Always", "optb": "Never", "optc": "Often", "optd": "Sometimes", "ans": "A", "explanation": "When a car suddenly starts the lower part of the boy's body will be in the motion while his upper will be at rest.\nHence he will always experience backward force:"}, {"question": "Which one of the following is always found in 'Wonder'?", "opta": "Crowd", "optb": "Lumber", "optc": "Astonishment", "optd": "Rustic", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Disclosure always involves", "opta": "Agents", "optb": "Display", "optc": "Exposition", "optd": "Secrets", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A bulb always has", "opta": "Glass", "optb": "Current", "optc": "Filament", "optd": "Light", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A mirror always", "opta": "Retracts", "optb": "Distorts", "optc": "Refracts", "optd": "Reflects", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A lotus flower always has", "opta": "Mud", "optb": "Petals", "optc": "Root", "optd": "Water", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In India a widow can marry her brother-in-law although a man cannot marry the sister of his dead wife:", "opta": "Always", "optb": "Never", "optc": "Often", "optd": "Sometimes", "ans": "D", "explanation": "As there is no such tradition hence this will happen sometimes."}, {"question": "Which one of the following is always found in 'Remedy of fault'?", "opta": "Punishment", "optb": "Remedy", "optc": "Fault", "optd": "Scolding", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A car always has", "opta": "Driver", "optb": "Wheels", "optc": "Bonnet", "optd": "Bumper", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Danger always involves", "opta": "Enemy", "optb": "Attack", "optc": "Fear", "optd": "Help", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A disease always has", "opta": "Cure", "optb": "Germs", "optc": "Cause", "optd": "Patient", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Management always involves", "opta": "Regulation", "optb": "Counsel", "optc": "Exhortation", "optd": "Coercion", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which one of the following is always found in 'Phrase'?", "opta": "Nomenclature", "optb": "Manifestation", "optc": "Pictorial effect", "optd": "Glossary", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If we are going early in the morning towards the south the sun will be visible at our left:", "opta": "Always", "optb": "Never", "optc": "Often", "optd": "Sometimes", "ans": "A", "explanation": "Early in the morning the sun is in the direction of east. If we are going towards the south, our face will be in the direction of South and our left hand will be in the direction of east.\nHence if we go early in the morning towards the south the sun will always be visible at our left."}, {"question": "My ten years old niece is taller than my twelve years old son:", "opta": "Always", "optb": "Never", "optc": "Often", "optd": "Sometimes", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is always in worry?", "opta": "Difficulty", "optb": "Unrest", "optc": "Non-Cooperation", "optd": "Poignancy", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which one of the following is always associated with 'tree'?", "opta": "Flowers", "optb": "Leaves", "optc": "Fruits", "optd": "Roots", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which one of the following is always associated with 'justice'?", "opta": "Hypocrisy", "optb": "Legitimate", "optc": "Magnanimity", "optd": "Diminutiveness", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A camera always has", "opta": "Reels", "optb": "Flash", "optc": "Stand", "optd": "Lens", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is found necessarily in a race?", "opta": "Judge", "optb": "Spectators", "optc": "Competitor", "optd": "Prize", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is found necessarily in game?", "opta": "Players", "optb": "Spectators", "optc": "Referee", "optd": "Victory", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which one of the following is always found in factories?", "opta": "Chimney", "optb": "Workers", "optc": "Electricity", "optd": "Sellers", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A hill always has", "opta": "Trees", "optb": "Height", "optc": "Animals", "optd": "Water", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which one of the following is always in 'Sentiment'?", "opta": "Cruelty", "optb": "Insight", "optc": "Neutrality", "optd": "Emotion", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Controversy always involves", "opta": "Dislike", "optb": "Injustice", "optc": "Disagreement", "optd": "Passion", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is found necessarily in newspaper?", "opta": "Date", "optb": "Advertisement", "optc": "News", "optd": "Editor", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}